DAVID IRVING

IT Project Manager

PROFILE

At my core, I believe in a person-toperson connection with clients and coworkers alike. Project management is arduous in that expectations, budgets, scopes, expectations, and timelines are always changing. My ability to make measured quick decisions makes me efficient at my job; however, I would argue, more important, is my ability to learn from experiences and apply them. Working to build relationships as well as managing the expectations of deadlines and budgets is something that sets me apart.

CONTACT

PHONE: 678.469.4930

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-jirving

GITHUB:

https://www.github.com/david-irving

PORTFOLIO:

http://www.davidirving.net

EMAIL:

David.Joseph.Irving@gmail.com

COMPUTER PROGRAM KNOWLEDGE:

Sales Force Sidekick E-automate Microsoft (All Applications) Monday

EDUCATION

Colorado Technical University

January 2018 – October 2019 M.S. in Information Technology, focus on Project Management

Oglethorpe University

May 2006 – October 2008

B.A. in Organizational Management

CERTIFICATION

Certified Scrum Master - ID 000987786

Scrum Alliance

WORK EXPERIENCE

Xerox Business Solutions Southwest - Network Project Manager February 2020 – Present

- Manage over forty accounts with a combined budget of \$5 million
- Coordinate logistics for installation or repair of multi-functional machines
- Schedule service technicians, IT analysis and operating with sales representatives, to ensure products and services delivered with customer satisfaction
- Ensure projects are on budget and in accordance with the timelines, and expectations of company, customer and state standards

Noodles and Company - General Manager

June 2017 – February 2020

- Implemented and managed company initiatives into a test store, including a full restaurant refresh and remodel project execution and changes
- Reduced weekly variance from by over 500%
- Facilitated the development and career growth of 7 shift managers and 2 Assistant General Managers; in addition, regularly mentored new associates in S.M.A.R.T. goal setting for their career advancement."
- Schedule compliance for 25+ employees
- Grew same store sales on a weekly average of over 14% compared to prior year in an industry expecting negative growth

hhgregg - Sales Manager

May 2016 - March 2017

- Directed and managed 3 store refreshes
- Designed and implemented a training program for all new associates, including working with them in S.M.A.R.T. goal setting and career development
- Responsible for the overall financial performance of the store
- Maintained compliance with standards and procedures for hhgregg
- Continuous and ongoing training of tenured associates to maintain knowledge and new industry standards

J. Alexander's - Assistant General Manager

February 2014 - May 2016

- Implemented and managed new training programs for employees
- Directed corporate project implementations as a test market for company-wide releases
- Directly responsible for all Liquor, Beer, and Wine ordering, invoicing, and inventory management while maintaining a loss of less than 2.3%
- Worked hand in hand with lower management, training and developing new bartenders and servers
- Managed the scheduling, training, and staffing over 50 servers, hosts, and bartenders